Laugh or get off the pot.
Tunnel Vision is a comedy film directed by Neal Israel.
A committee investigating TV's first uncensored network examines a typical day's
programming, which includes shows, commercials, news programs, you name it.
What they discover will surely crack you up!
This outrageous and irreverent spoof of television launched the
careers of some of the greatest comedians of all time.
Christian A. Broder, played by Phil Proctor.
Senator McMannus, played by Howard Hesseman.
Senator Polanski, played by Dan Barrows.
Proctologist, played by Stephen Feinberg.
Chevy Chase, played by Chevy Chase.
Cooper, played by John Candy.
TunnelVision (also known as Tunnel Vision) is a satirical 1976 comedy anthology film featuring Roger Bowen, Chevy Chase, John Candy, Howard Hesseman, Joe Flaherty, Laraine
Newman, Betty Thomas, Phil Proctor, Al Franken, Ron Silver, Tom Davis, and Michael Overly, with appearances by voiceover artists Ernie Anderson and Danny Dark.
It was directed by Neal Israel and Bradley R.
Swirnoff and produced by Joe Roth.
Although the title is repeatedly displayed in the film as being spelled "Tunnelvision",
it is frequently identified as "Tunnel Vision" in home video reissues.
The tone is lighthearted.